Ice cream is my favorite food, but I
can't just eat 1,000 calories of fat and
sugar every night. So, thank God for the
Ninja Creamy because this thing allows
me to recreate my favorite ice cream
flavors, but low calorie and high
protein. I was feeling pretty festive
this week, so I made a mint Oreo, which
was phenomenal. And then this peppermint
mocha, which tasted exactly like
Starbucks peppermint mocha, but ice
cream. And I made a chocolate peanut
butter Oreo because it is one of my
favorite flavors of all time. And then I
made some recipes for a brand deal that
I'm working on. This was a vanilla bean.
And then I also made a Reese's flavor.
Try to guess the brand. I bet you're not
going to get it. But these were
phenomenal. Shout out to that brand. And
also go pick up a Ninja Creamy if you
don't have one already. They're still on
sale and it makes the perfect holiday